<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Titi</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Titi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Institutional investors entry to the crypto space</title>
      <link>/posts/investors-crypto-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/investors-crypto-space/</guid>
      <description>Overall, institutional investors are positive about crypto assets. The influx of institutional investors stalled by the unexpectedly harsh bear market that hit near the end of 2018. Institutional investors are searching for crypto assets that meet their goals and fit into their portfolios while staying within their risk tolerance levels. Knowledge of crypto assets ranges from novice to expert across the field. Coinbase’s Christine Sandler explains that the main barriers for institutional investors are: regulation ambiguity and the lack of institutional products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loans backed by crypto assets and their liquidity promise</title>
      <link>/posts/crypto-loans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/crypto-loans/</guid>
      <description>As a result of the crypto bear market in 2018, many crypto-based companies are illiquid. Among these companies are crypto-mining firms and startups which raised funds in the form of digital coins. Most crypto holders don’t want to sell their digital tokens at these depressed prices and are expecting a rebound in the market. There is a new breed of startups: crypto loan companies, which aim at providing liquidity to the crypto market space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security tokens and the promise to democratize the patents industry</title>
      <link>/posts/security-tokens-patents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/security-tokens-patents/</guid>
      <description>The current patent and intellectual property (IP) market is very opaque. Many manual processes and middlemen make it a cumbersome and not attractive market. According to the World Intellectual Property Organization, the IP market is worth $180 billion annually. IPWe is creating the first global online patent marketplace where companies can license, sell and acquire patents. IPWe platform uses blockchain to store patents and transactions over patents. IPWe uses artificial intelligence to allow customers make smart searches within the entire patent register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provoking Thinking</title>
      <link>/metodologia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/metodologia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>